{
  "categoryList": [
    {
      "categoryName": "Math",
      "categoryUsage": 0,
      "questionList": [
        {
          "questionText": "Continue this pattern: 144, 121, 100, 81, 64",
          "correctAnswer": "49",
          "wrongAnswer1": "48",
          "wrongAnswer2": "47",
          "wrongAnswer3": "51",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Solve this: (32 x 8) + 104 - 27",
          "correctAnswer": "333",
          "wrongAnswer1": "301",
          "wrongAnswer2": "408",
          "wrongAnswer3": "395",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "123x123= ?",
          "correctAnswer": "15129",
          "wrongAnswer1": "15123",
          "wrongAnswer2": "18123",
          "wrongAnswer3": "32879",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is 0.3 as a fraction?",
          "correctAnswer": "3/10",
          "wrongAnswer1": "10/9",
          "wrongAnswer2": "10/3",
          "wrongAnswer3": "3289",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the square root of 576?",
          "correctAnswer": "24",
          "wrongAnswer1": "3,57",
          "wrongAnswer2": "23",
          "wrongAnswer3": "26",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What are all the prime numbers between 20 and 30?",
          "correctAnswer": "23 and 29",
          "wrongAnswer1": "21 and 27",
          "wrongAnswer2": "23 and 30",
          "wrongAnswer3": "25 and 29",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is 75% as a fraction in simplest form? ",
          "correctAnswer": "3/4",
          "wrongAnswer1": "0.25",
          "wrongAnswer2": "0.12",
          "wrongAnswer3": "4/3",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The value of x + x(x) when x = 2 is: ?",
          "correctAnswer": "6",
          "wrongAnswer1": "16",
          "wrongAnswer2": "8",
          "wrongAnswer3": "12",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the square root of 3 times the square root of 3?",
          "correctAnswer": "3",
          "wrongAnswer1": "9",
          "wrongAnswer2": "12",
          "wrongAnswer3": "27",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is 1/5th of 25? ",
          "correctAnswer": "5",
          "wrongAnswer1": "10",
          "wrongAnswer2": "25",
          "wrongAnswer3": "50",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        }
      ]

    },
    {
      "categoryName": "IT",
      "categoryUsage": 0,
      "questionList": [
        {
          "questionText": "What is the meaning of CPU?",
          "correctAnswer": "Central Processing Unit",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Critical Processing Unit",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Crucial Processing Unit",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Central Printing Unit",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "How many bits make a byte?",
          "correctAnswer": "8 bits",
          "wrongAnswer1": "16 bits",
          "wrongAnswer2": "12 bits",
          "wrongAnswer3": "24 bits",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The process of starting or restarting a computer is called",
          "correctAnswer": "Booting",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Start up point",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Connecting",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Resetting",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is 'Intranet'? ",
          "correctAnswer": "Internal network designed to serve the internal informational needs of a single organization.",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Internal internet used to transfer information internally.",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Internal internet used to transfer information to the outside company.",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Internal network designed to transfer the information between two organization",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is ISP and what is their functions?",
          "correctAnswer": "Internet Service Provider. A company which provide internet connection to other people for a fee",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Intenal Service Provider. A company which provide internet connection for a fee",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Internet Service Provider. A company which provide internal transferring data service to an organization",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Internal Service Provider. A company provide internal connection to transfer data between two company",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "HTTP stand for",
          "correctAnswer": "Hyper Text Transport Protocol",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Hyper Transport Text Protocol",
          "wrongAnswer2": "High Text Transport Protocol",
          "wrongAnswer3": "High Transport Text Protocol",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "How many computer languages are in use?",
          "correctAnswer": "2000",
          "wrongAnswer1": "50",
          "wrongAnswer2": "500",
          "wrongAnswer3": "150",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Which of these is not an early computer?",
          "correctAnswer": "NASA",
          "wrongAnswer1": "SAGE",
          "wrongAnswer2": "ENIAC",
          "wrongAnswer3": "UNIVAC",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "\"Which of the following is not one of the early 'protocols', or ways to use the Internet?",
          "correctAnswer": "Blogging",
          "wrongAnswer1": "FTP",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Telenet",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Gopher",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
          "correctAnswer": "Yahoo",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Google Chat",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Intranet",
          "wrongAnswer3": "WWW",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "categoryName": "Geography",
      "categoryUsage": 0,
      "questionList": [
        {
          "questionText": "Which river flows through Paris??",
          "correctAnswer": "Seine",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Nile",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Danube",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Ganges",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is Europe’s largest port?",
          "correctAnswer": "Port of Rotterdam",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Port of Dalian",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Port of Mangalia",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Port of Odessa",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In which country is the UK’s highest mountain, Ben Nevis?",
          "correctAnswer": "Scotland",
          "wrongAnswer1": "UK",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Germany",
          "wrongAnswer3": "France",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Mount Vesuvius overlooks which modern Italian city?",
          "correctAnswer": "Naples",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Florence",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Venice",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Rome",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Of which country is Sofia the capital?",
          "correctAnswer": "Bulgaria",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Turkey",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Germany",
          "wrongAnswer3": "France",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Apart from Dutch and French, what is the other official language of Belgium?",
          "correctAnswer": "German",
          "wrongAnswer1": "English",
          "wrongAnswer2": "French",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Romanian",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Which river forms part of the boundary between Mexico and the United States?",
          "correctAnswer": "Rio Grande",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Mississippi River",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Ohio River",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Dakota Creek",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the longest river flowing in India?",
          "correctAnswer": "Ganges",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Punarbhaba",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Bagmati",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Gumti",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What does each star on the flag of the United States stand for?",
          "correctAnswer": "A state",
          "wrongAnswer1": "A city",
          "wrongAnswer2": "A river",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Freedom",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Which country is Luxembourg the capital of?",
          "correctAnswer": "Luxembourg",
          "wrongAnswer1": "UK",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Germany",
          "wrongAnswer3": "France",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "categoryName": "History",
      "categoryUsage": 0,
      "questionList": [
        {
          "questionText": "In what year did Christopher Columbus land in North America?",
          "correctAnswer": "1492",
          "wrongAnswer1": "1552",
          "wrongAnswer2": "1332",
          "wrongAnswer3": "1997",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "In ancient Egypt, people shaved their eyebrows when this animal died: ",
          "correctAnswer": "cat",
          "wrongAnswer1": "dog",
          "wrongAnswer2": "lobster",
          "wrongAnswer3": "ox",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is not one of the 7 Wonders of the Ancient World?",
          "correctAnswer": "The Island of Atlantis",
          "wrongAnswer1": "The Temple of Artemis",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Statue of Zeus at Olympia",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Lighthouse of Alexandria",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Ancient Egypt was conquered in 30 B.C. by which Empire?",
          "correctAnswer": "Roman",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Mongolian",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Greek",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Achaemenid",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Henry VIII married this amount of times:",
          "correctAnswer": "6",
          "wrongAnswer1": "8",
          "wrongAnswer2": "5",
          "wrongAnswer3": "3",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Roman Emperor Caligula made his ____ an official Senator.",
          "correctAnswer": "horse",
          "wrongAnswer1": "cat",
          "wrongAnswer2": "son",
          "wrongAnswer3": "friend",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What's the name of the first western explorer to reach China?",
          "correctAnswer": "Marco Polo",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Sir Walter Raleigh",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Ferdinand Magellan",
          "wrongAnswer3": "None of the above",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The Bubonic Plague ravaged Europe in this century: ",
          "correctAnswer": "14th",
          "wrongAnswer1": "13th",
          "wrongAnswer2": "12th",
          "wrongAnswer3": "9th",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Which country did the Magna Carta originate in? ",
          "correctAnswer": "England",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Spain",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Italy",
          "wrongAnswer3": "France",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What was Mickey Mouse originally called?",
          "correctAnswer": "Mortimer Mouse",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Martin Mouse",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Keith Mouse",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Michael Mouse",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "categoryName": "English",
      "categoryUsage": 0,
      "questionList": [
        {
          "questionText": "The thief was sent to __ prison",
          "correctAnswer": "the",
          "wrongAnswer1": "a",
          "wrongAnswer2": "an",
          "wrongAnswer3": "no article",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Which of the following is a verb in its infinitive form?",
          "correctAnswer": "To run",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Running",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Will run",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Ran",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What kind of sentence ends in a question mark?",
          "correctAnswer": "Interrogative",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Exclamatory",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Declarative",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Imperative",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "George hurt his head while he __.",
          "correctAnswer": "was ice skating",
          "wrongAnswer1": "ice skates",
          "wrongAnswer2": "ice skated",
          "wrongAnswer3": "had ice skated",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Max ___ for the CIA since 1992.",
          "correctAnswer": "has been working",
          "wrongAnswer1": "will work",
          "wrongAnswer2": "works",
          "wrongAnswer3": "is working",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The last time I ____ to Korea, I spent three weeks on Cheju island.",
          "correctAnswer": "went",
          "wrongAnswer1": "have gone",
          "wrongAnswer2": "was going",
          "wrongAnswer3": "will go",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Before Jack arrived, Jill ____ up the hill.",
          "correctAnswer": "had already gone",
          "wrongAnswer1": "has already gone",
          "wrongAnswer2": "is already going",
          "wrongAnswer3": "was going",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "It ____ every day since I arrived here.",
          "correctAnswer": "has rained",
          "wrongAnswer1": "rains",
          "wrongAnswer2": "will rain",
          "wrongAnswer3": "rained",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What word has no plural?",
          "correctAnswer": "Money",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Car",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Dog",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Triangle",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "'Tense' is a grammatical category that applies to: ",
          "correctAnswer": "verbs",
          "wrongAnswer1": "adverbs",
          "wrongAnswer2": "nouns",
          "wrongAnswer3": "adjectives",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        }

      ]
    },
    {
      "categoryName": "Biology",
      "categoryUsage": 0,
      "questionList": [
        {
          "questionText": "Which of these units is most suitable for measuring the length of a cell?",
          "correctAnswer": "Micrometre",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Metre",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Kilometre",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Centrimetre",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Plants receive their nutrients mainly from: ",
          "correctAnswer": "Soil",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Atmosphere",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Light",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Air",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "A person who studies biology is known as a?",
          "correctAnswer": "Biologist",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Scientist",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Physician",
          "wrongAnswer3": "None of the above",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Aspirin comes from which of the following?",
          "correctAnswer": "Willow bark",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Oak tree",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Acacia",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Eucalyptus",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "Carrot is orange in color because?",
          "correctAnswer": "It contains carotene",
          "wrongAnswer1": "It grows in the soil",
          "wrongAnswer2": "It is not exposed to sunlight",
          "wrongAnswer3": "The entire plant is orange in color",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The rarest blood group is: ",
          "correctAnswer": "AB negative",
          "wrongAnswer1": "B negative",
          "wrongAnswer2": "AB positive",
          "wrongAnswer3": "O negative",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The metal present in the haemoglobin is: ",
          "correctAnswer": "Iron",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Copper",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Calcium",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Aluminium",
          "questionDifficulty": 2
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The longest and largest bone in the human body is: ",
          "correctAnswer": "Femur",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Spinal Cord",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Humerus",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Fibula",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "What is the Ph value of human blood?",
          "correctAnswer": "7.40",
          "wrongAnswer1": "7",
          "wrongAnswer2": "0",
          "wrongAnswer3": "8",
          "questionDifficulty": 1
        },
        {
          "questionText": "The important sugar in honey is: ",
          "correctAnswer": "Fructose",
          "wrongAnswer1": "Lactose",
          "wrongAnswer2": "Maltose",
          "wrongAnswer3": "Sucrose",
          "questionDifficulty": 3
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}